geeky-gadgets.com 2018-12-31

# Privacy Policy

### Who we are?

At geeky-gadgets.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use and visit geeky-gadgets.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### Types of data we collect

#### Website Cookies

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums. We use third party tracking systems like Google Analytics, Whois and to monitor the amount visitors we have to our website, we do not record any of your personal information.

We also use third party advertisements on geeky-gadgets.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

Deleting cookies does not mean you are permanently opted out of any advertising program. Unless you have settings that disallow cookies, the next time you visit a site running the advertisements, a new cookie will be added.

You can find out more information about advertising cookies and how you can disable them over at the [your online choices](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/about-behavioural-advertising) website.

You can also change your preferences in your web browser to control cookies for the websites you visit, how this is done varies on your individual browser, please refer to your browser help section for more information on how this can be done.

#### DoubleClick DART cookies

We also may use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”). The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers. You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx

#### Google Analytics

When someone visits www.~Geeky-Gadgets.com we use a third party service, Google Analytics, to collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information is only processed in a way which does not identify anyone. We do not make, and do not allow Google to make, any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our website.

### Use of data

Geeky Gadgets uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our website and our service.
  * To notify you about changes to our website.
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
  * To monitor the usage of our website
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news and information.

### What is GDPR?

The EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) replaces the Data Protection Directive 95/46/EC and was designed to harmonize data privacy laws across Europe, to protect and empower all EU citizens data privacy and to reshape the way organizations across the region approach data privacy. The key articles of the GDPR, as well as information on its business impact, can be found throughout this site. Full details can be found at the **[GDPR website](https://www.eugdpr.org/)**.

### Your rights

As a user of Geeky Gadgets you have the following rights:

  * The right to ask what personal data that we hold about you at any time.
  * The right to ask us to update and correct any out-of-date or incorrect personal data that we hold about you free of charge.
  * As set out above, the right to opt out of any marketing communications that we may send you.

You can find out more information about your rights over at the [**Information Commissioner’s Office**](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/).

### Your Agreement.

Your use of our website or Services evidences your agreement to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

Please read Our Privacy Policy carefully. By accessing or using this website, you acknowledge that you have read, understand and agree to our Privacy Policy and our website terms. **If you do not agree with these terms, please exit this page.**

 _ **Updated 21st May 2108 to comply with the new European data protection requirements.** _
